Start  Game
2 visible cards drawn at random; 1st draw goes to computer
A 2nd card drawn for both computer and player; Players card is
  visible to players only. Computer card is visible to computer
  only.
  
A = 11 unless total score > 21;
A = 1 if total score > 21;

If Computer score = 21; game over
If player score = 21 & computer score <> 21; game over

Computer decides whether to Stay or Hit
  Logic: computer will Hit if score < 17
Player decides whether to Stay or Hit
  If total score > 21; player loses

